Pathakamuri Siddartha

Software Engineer

About 2.6 years of strong experience as a MEAN and MERN stack developer with solid understanding of front-end technologies and moderate database designing, I have worked on a wide variety of projects, from small-scale websites to complex web applications And I am constantly seeking out new ways to innovate and push the boundaries of what is possible on the web.



xiddusiddartha2000@gmail.com

Pradipatri, Andhra Pradesh, India

in linkedin.com/in/pathakamuri-siddartha-671a9415a

7287992262

3 July, 2000

github.com/Siddartha03

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Great Software Laboratory PVT LTD

07/2021 - Present

Pune, India

Software Engineer Intern

Great Software Laboratory PVT LTD

01/2021 - 07/2021

Pune, India

PROJECTS

Portal to Provision VM (01/2023 - Present)

- Portal to provision VM wishes to offer a best-in-class web portal. It
 will enable allocating multiple VM for individual or organization. It
 will enable multiple roles and integration to have complete control
 on allocation.
- Developed UI using ReactJs, React-Redux, Redux-Saga. Third party login implementation, UI customization and many more.

Automation Studio AngularJS to Angular 14 migration (04/2022 - 12/2022)

- Admin module pages/components developed in Angular.js need to be migrated to Angular 14. This is done using the exone custom UI components library and follows the best standards for UX Frontend code.
- Developed using Angular 14 / Ag-Grid / cxone custom UI library / Jasmine & Karma / Cypress (E2E testing) .

REST based APIs CLI development (10/2021 - 02/2022)

- The REST based APIs Command Line Interface provides a unified interface for interacting with the Administrative System. It offers multiple interactive features for listing available profiles, environments, or applications, checking-in and checking-out of profiles.
- Developed using Oclif CLI framework.

Book My Seat Application (03/2021 - 09/2021)

- The Book My Seat application is to facilitate administrators and above to reserve seats for their team members in advance, during the pandemic situation.
- Developed using Angular / Angular Material / NodeJs / MongoDB.

EDUCATION

B.Tech (Computer Science & Engineering)Lovely Professional University

SKILLS

 ReactJs
 Angular
 React Native
 Redux

 Cypress
 NodeJs
 CLI development
 Oclif

 MongoDB
 HTML
 SCSS
 JavaScript
 Git

ACHIEVEMENTS

PAT ON THE BACK (07/2021)

Award for contributing to the angular UI as well as node.js backend in Book My Seat application, taking initiatives and going the extra mile in identifying critical bugs and finding solutions to fix the problems.

CERTIFICATES

Node.js (05/2020 - 07/2020)

I have successfully undergone Back-end development course in Simplilearn. The training program consists of Nodejs and Mongodb

Full Stack Web Development (06/2019 - 08/2019)

This is the summer training program in Board Infinity. In this program i learned HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ReactJs, Node.js and MongoDB.

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

HOBBIES

Reading tech news

Playing Badminton

Travelling